Deliverance in Jesus' Name
Stand up!
What was the problem you had before?
A very serious ulcer pain here.
So, as you were preaching there, I said,
"If you are a man of God, when you touch me and this pain goes, I will know".
As you touched me, I can't feel the pain - for over 20 years.
You can't see what?
There's no pain again.
What kind of pain?
Ulcer pain.
For how many years?
It's more than 22 years.
But after touching you, what happened?
I'm not feeling it anymore.
It's gone!
The SCOAN Sunday Service
Thank You, Jesus!
I allowed him to talk out of many I have touched.
I don't just touch you. What will I derive from touching you and you falling down?
Sometimes when I touch you and you don't fall, I still want to touch you
until that thing leaves you.
I know what is leaving you.
You may not know.
At least almost four people I touched here - poverty left them.
The SCOAN Sunday Service
But the problem many of you have is that when you are touched like that,
because you do not advertise your problem, before touching you, you keep to yourself.
I will never forget who is the light when I come out from where?
Darkness.
Now you are coming out of darkness but you keep the light.
From darkness to light.
From darkness to light - those problems are darkness.
PROPHECY CONFIRMATION
My name is Honourable Jones Dangba. I'm from Abuja (Nigeria).
We were asked to come for interview, to state what was wrong with us.
Since I didn't have a medical report for ulcer, I didn't include it.
So at midnight I woke up and said,
"Well, God, this is the arena of liberty.
If this is a man of God and I believe he is because that is why I came,
prove that he is a man of God".
He came behind me and touched me. I said, "This is it!"
Immediately I stood up, he just took his hand and hit directly.
You can't touch the spot with your finger.
He hit the hand directly and I fell down.
He went round, came back again and hit me again.
As I touched the stomach, no single pain!
I had this problem for the last 21 years.
My father has gone to be with the Lord.
He had the same ulcer issue.
My mother has the ulcer issue.
I had the same ulcer issue, and I said,
"God, this thing must end with me!"
Even my little daughter, who is now a youth copper, also has the problem.
I said, "No, this is generational; it must end with me today!"
But what surprised me was that I didn't include it
and I only spoke to God in my heart, "If this is a man of God, let him detect this fault".
And he hit me there and as I stand here,
I have never seen this type of healing before, since I was born.
Totally free! God detected the ulcer! I'm healed!
Amen. Let's put our hands together for Jesus Christ!
So, you mean to say, sir, that as the prophet was moving around,
the exact spot where he touched you
was the exact area you'd had this severe stomach ulcer for over twenty years.
Yes, exactly 21 years.
He hit it; he didn't just touch me.
I want to thank God that this is my own gift for the year!
I have crossed my bridge. Amen.
Thank You, Jesus Christ.
Sir, just tell us - before coming to The SCOAN,
what were the kind of pains you were in because of this ulcer
and how did it affect your life negatively?
I couldn't eat pepper as such; I couldn't.
If I ate a particular food, I had to buy medication and take it.
They know me in a particular pharmacy behind my house.
I used to say, "Give me anything anti-ulcer".
When they saw me, the pharmacist would say, "Anything anti-ulcer!"
So every week, I finished one packet.
When I ate, I had to take it.
Otherwise, I would have to complain. I would not sleep well.
Right now, sir, can you just touch the area where you were having the problem.
This is the matter now; I'm not feeling it.
Thank You, Lord Jesus, for healing me!